{
    "id": "d9bab78ef55c4353912a47807063e3cd",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is rich ………………….. he is not happy.",
            "description": "We use but to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d81243610c14ecc876550a24546f3ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sells oranges …………………… mangoes.",
            "description": "We use as well as to add.",
            "answers": [
                "as well",
                "also",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ef3a787da89d4cef90a961269a7c0c7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I honor him ………………… he is an honest man.",
            "description": "We use because to give the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5bd0d5a133424dbd9c6333909d49e884"
        },
        {
            "question": "We decided to go out ……………….. it was very late.",
            "description": "We use although to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "however",
                "even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f11defbc22f746d186e61b98fcf605a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat down ………………… he was tired.",
            "description": "We use because to give the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "72b17e3a54e84ae99a316ce52d0d5e52"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must be quiet …………………. you must leave the room.",
            "description": "We use or to present an alternative.",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "while",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "809e8497c74b418295e2a3d90f47aaf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is neither a knave ……………….. a fool.",
            "description": "We can combine two negative ideas with neither…nor.",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "either",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa0d0b4b6d244180aa53367a6eba7e8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will come …………………. I have time.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "066089d2599943928e71885e3777ea11"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the shop ……………….. bought some pens.",
            "description": "We use and to merely add one statement to another.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "to",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c09ab896e6a0409f9e105a2c82d83a17"
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for him ………………… he arrived.",
            "description": "We use until to show time.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "without",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e956def609654003bc69b8a199ea072b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He bled so profusely ……………… he died.",
            "description": "The conjunction so that can express cause and effect.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a1207dfadc1e468793cb461e309d1239"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the prize ……………….. you deserve it.",
            "description": "We use unless to express a condition. It is similar to if not.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e56b96468b074c51a85060e7f2f5dbcd"
        }
    ]
}